ReMastered: Devil at the Crossroads is a music,
documentary film directed by Brian Oakes.
Robert Johnson was one of the most influential blues guitarists ever.
Even before his early death, fans wondered if he'd made a pact with the Devil.
Self, played by Keith Richards.
Self, played by Keb' Mo'.
Self, played by Taj Mahal.
Self, played by Bonnie Raitt.
Self, played by Eric Clapton.
Self, played by John Hammond.
ReMastered: Devil at the Crossroads is a 2019 documentary film about
Robert Johnson, the blues singer, songwriter and musician.
It was released on April 26, 2019 on Netflix streaming.
The film explores themes of blues, guitar player,
singer-songwriter, blues music, robert johnson.